

BLK 138, BEDOK NORTH ST 2, SINGAPORE - 460138

M +65-9277 4584

hello@priyeshtungare.com www.priyeshtungare.com

PROFILE

I have 9 years of IT experience, spanning across Retail, Life-sciences, Pharmaceutical and Telecom Software domains. Currently working as Senior Consultant with IBM Ireland Product Distribution Limited, Singapore Branch.

I have been involved in all phases of the Systems Development Life Cycle including define, design, development, test, deployment, and support and maintenance for IBM Sterling Commerce (CPQ and OMS).

I'm a self-taught and passionate Front-End Developer with intermediate knowledge of back-end technologies.

I have been <u>self-learning</u> Front End Development for the past 7 months. I have taken courses on FreeCodeCamp, Codecademy and Teamtreehouse to pursue a career in Front-End Development.

SKILLS

FRONT-END & BACK-END SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Sass / Bootstrap
- Bourbon / Neat
- JavaScript / jQuery
- Angular JS
- Ajax
- Version Control (GIT)
- Ruby / Ruby on Rails (Limited)
- Node.js / express.js (Beginner)
- MongoDB (Beginner)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- IBM Sterling CPQ
- IBM Sterling OMS
- IBM DB2
- IBM WebSphere Application Server
- Agile Development
- SDLC
- Java
- XML / XSLT
- Application Deployment
- Web logic
- Requirements Gathering & Analysis
- Project Planning & Team Management

EXPERIENCED IN

- IBM Sterling CPQ Visual Modeler for Model Development, Customisations for Sterling Configurator, Rules Creation
- IBM Sterling Business Center Catalog Administration, Item Administration, Pricing Administration, Data Loading etc
- IBM Sterling Field Sales Quote Creation, Quote to Order Process, Pricing Adjustment etc
- IBM Sterling Order Management Participant Modelling, Process Modelling, Agent Architecture and implementation, Data Loading, UI Customisations, Inventory Management, DOM, Sourcing and Scheduling, Payment Processing etc
- Project Management activities like Project Plan creation, delivery schedule, Project estimations etc
- Trained in IBM Architectural Thinking Process
- · Providing training to new team members on IBM Sterling CPQ

WORK EXPERIENCE

IBM Singapore - Senior Consultant Mar 2012 - Present

- Responsible for creating Project Plan for model development and testing activities and ensure that the plan is followed as per schedule.
- Responsible for delivering new SaaS product models using Sterling CPQ 9.2. Involved in developing Configurator Framework, Configurator Rules to handle complex business logic.
- Involved in Creating Configurable Items, creating Pricing rules, PriceLists using SBC.
- Involved in end to end testing of the application using Sterling Field Sales and Passport Advantage.
- Involved in submitting Project Estimations for Sterling OMS project. Worked on POCs involving various modules of Sterling OMS such as UI Customisations, Agent Architecture, DOM, GIV etc.
- Training new team members on IBM Sterling CPQ.
- Involved in submitting Project Estimations for Sterling OMS project. Worked on POCs involving various modules of Sterling OMS such as UI Customisations, Agent Architecture, DOM, GIV etc

IBM Singapore - Associate Consultant Aug 2015 - Oct 2015

This project involved design and setup of IBM Control Center (ICC) for one of the leading bank in South-East Asia. The client wanted to setup ICC to manage their Sterling Connect:Direct Servers.

Responsibilities included but are not limited to:

- Installation and configuration of ICC on UAT and Production Servers.
- Creation of custom rules, DVGs, SLCs etc on both UAT and Production Servers.
- Creation of scripts to create custom rules, users, managing servers in ICC
- Installation and Configuration of IBM Sterling External Authentication Server to implement extended authentication to ICC using LDAP.
- Configuration of Cognos Reports and Connection for IBM Control Center
- Tuning of the Production Server
- Installation and Configuration documentation for IBM Control Center, IBM Sterling External Authentication Server

Astrazeneca, Macclesfield, United Kingdom - Release Manager Sep 2011 - Mar 2012

- Involved in the Release Planning and Co-ordination for the Ariba OnDemand and Change Demand suites that were
 developed for the client into Client network.
- Main responsibility was to configure the Configuration management tool on which the code packages will be stored
 and deployed later on during the release.
- It also involved Co-ordination with different stakeholders to understand the schedule and plan the release as per the schedule etc.

Sage, Newcastle Upon Tyne, United Kingdom - Consultant Sep 2010 - Apr 2011

- This project involved design and launch of the Accounting Software products developed by client for Small-Scale and Mid-Scale Business firms in UK. Comergent had the profile, product, catalog, pricing and Configurator modules implemented and interfaces with the downstream order management and CRM Systems.
- This project involved the creation of service contracts and maintenance contracts for the Sage Accounts Products, Sage 50 Accounts Products, Sage 100 Products, PSPL products etc. The main task was to create the products and configure them according to the market requirement using the Sterling Visual Modeler and Sterling Configurator module of Comergent.
- As a Sterling Configurator Consultant, my main role was to create and develop products using the Sterling Visual Modeler and Sterling Configurator, verifying the Configuration Rules written, Configuration Validation, and Unit Testing of the models.

Infosys Technologies Ltd, Mangalore, India - Senior Software Engineer & Team Lead Jul 2007 - Mar 2012

- Design, develop and implement applications that support day-to-day operations.
- Develop and implement assigned modules in the project
- Responding promptly and professionally to bug reports.
- Responsible for developing new programs and proofing the program to develop needed changes to assure production of a quality product.
- Interface with clients and gather business requirements and objectives.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, University of Mumbai - 2007

AWARDS & RECOGNITION

- Two time recipient of Manager Awards in IBM Singapore
- Selected for 'IBM Leadership program to create Future Leaders' Program in IBM Singapore
- Recipient of Best Project Team in Infosys Technologies Ltd

CERTIFICATIONS

- IBM Certified Deployment Professional Sterling Configurator V9.1
- IBM Certified Deployment Professional Sterling Order Management V9.1